Most motorcycles run on petrol, this one runs on blood!
I Bought a Vampire Motorcycle is a comedy, horror
film directed by Dirk Campbell.
When a motorbike gang kills an occultist, the evil spirit
he was summoning inhabits a damaged bike.
The bike is then bought and restored, but reveals its true nature when it tries to
exact vengance on the gang, and anyone else who gets in its way.
Noddy, played by Neil Morrissey.
Kim, played by Amanda Noar.
Inspector Cleaver, played by Michael Elphick.
Priest, played by Anthony Daniels.
Roach, played by Andrew Powell.
Chopper, played by George Rossi.
I Bought a Vampire Motorcycle is a 1990 British comedy horror film about a motorcycle possessed by an evil
spirit, which rides by itself and kills people, particularly members of a particular motorcycle gang.
It stars Neil Morrissey as the bike's owner, Michael Elphick as a police inspector, and
Anthony Daniels as a priest who attempts to exorcise the bike's evil spirit.
The film explores themes of supernatural, motorcycle, vampirism, birmingham.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.